<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<?xml-model href="dharmaChecker.sch" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<root>

<chapter> 
<l num = "1"><original><mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "scratch">Hopping a freight out of Los Angeles</mark> at high noon one day in late September </original></l>
<l num = "2"><original>1955<mark location = "belowline" color = "blue" shape = "carrot, comma"></mark> I got on a gondola and lay down with my duff<mark location = "inline" color = "blue" shape = "squiggle"></mark>le bag under my head and my</original></l>
<l num = "3"><original>knees crossed and contemplated the clouds as we rolled north to Santa Barbara.</original></l>
<l num = "4"><original><mark location = "aboveline" color = "blue" shape = "swoosh">It</mark> was a local<mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "semicolon "></mark> and I intended to sleep on the beach at Santa Barbara that night</original></l>
<l num = "5"><original>and catch either another local to San Luis Obispo the next morning or the </original></l>
<l num = "6"><original>first<mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "circle"></mark>class freight all the way to San Francisco at <mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "circle">7</mark> <mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "slash">p.m.</mark> <mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "line">at night</mark><mark location = "inline" color = "gray" shape = "slash">.</mark> Somewhere </original></l>
<l num = "7"><original>near Camarillo where <mark location = "aboveline" color = "blue" shape = "word">Charley</mark> Parker'd been mad and relaxed back to normal health,</original></l>
<l num = "8"><original>a thin old little<mark location = "aboveline" color = "gray" shape = "check"></mark> bum climbed into my gondola as we headed into a siding to give</original></l>
<l num = "9"><original> a train right of way and looked surprised to see me there. He established him-</original></l>
<l num = "10"><original>self at the other end of the gondola and lay down, facing me, with his head on</original></l>
<l num = "11"><original> his own miserably small pack and said nothing. By and by they blew the</original></l>
<l num = "12"><original> highball whistle after the eastbound freight had smashed through on the main line</original></l>
<l num = "13"><orignal>and we pulled out as the air got colder and fog began to blow from the sea over the</orignal></l>
<l num = "14"><original> warm valleys of the coast. Both the little bum and I, after un­successful attempts</original></l>
<l num = "15"><original> to huddle on the cold steel in wraparounds, got up and paced back and forth and </original></l>
<l num = "16"><original>jumped and flapped arms at each our end of the gon. Pretty soon we headed into</original></l>
<l num = "17"><original>"another siding at a small railroad town and I figured I needed a poor-boy of Tokay</original></l>
<l num = "18"><original>wine to complete the cold dusk run to Santa Barbara. <dialogue character = "">"Will you watch my pack</dialogue></original></l>
<l num = "19"><original><dialogue character = "">while I run over there and get a bottle of wine?"</dialogue></original></l>

<l num = "20"><original><dialogue character = "poor boy">"Sure thing."</dialogue> I jumped over the side and ran across Highway 101</original></l>
<l num = "21"><original> to the store, and bought, besides wine, a little bread and candy. I ran back to </original></l>
<l num = "22"><original> my freight train which had another fifteen minutes to wait in the now warm sunny scene.</original></l>
<l num = "23"><original>But it was late after­noon and bound to get cold soon. The little bum was sitting </original></l>
<l num = "24"><original>crosslegged at his end before a pitiful repast of one can of sardines. I took</original></l>

<l num = "25"><original><dialogue character = "">"How about a little wine to warm you up? Maybe you'd like some bread</dialogue></original></l>
<l num = "26"><original><dialogue character = ""> pity on him and went over and said, and cheese with your sardines."</dialogue></original></l>
</chapter>
</root>
